Biden admin officials admitting that the pressure on them to call for a ceasefire is becoming undeniable.
All the calling, emailing and protesting is working.
This is coming from Dear White Staffers.
Dear White Staffers is a page that basically shares anonymous information from staffers that are working on the Hill.
Staffers are the folks that are working in these offices.
They're fielding the phone calls.
They are helping.
They're assisting, you know, senators and congresspeople, etc.
They're the boots that are moving when we see these people on TV grooving.
In fact, there is recognition within the administration, and this is highlighted,
some of the president's close advisors believe there are only weeks, not months,
until rebuffing the pressure on the U.S. government to publicly call for a ceasefire becomes untenable.
Rebuffing means to reject.
Untenable means unable to maintain.
So before your feeds go back to normal, hold the line.
Hold it.
We are in a society that has become so obsessed with instant gratification that we seem to think that anything that requires us to literally, like,
stay the course beyond the smallest amount of uncomfortability is just like, ugh, it's a lost cause.
And it's not.
Stay the course.